Thank you for watching!
Here you go, here we go!
It's time for the "Halo! Stee, this time with Yuki Hirayama of Angulum,
Kurumi Takase of Beyons Ame no Mori Kawakami.
These two will be presenting this time, so please stay with us until the end.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Now, Hello! Project 2023 SUMMER CITY CIRCUIT is in full swing.
Yay. It has begun.
It has started.
We, Beyonce and Angulum, have now finished the Osaka show,
The next show for Angulum will be in Sendai on August 5, and for Beyoncé on August 13,
And Beyonce will perform in Kanagawa on August 13th.
Yes, I'm looking forward to it.
How is the summer tour coming along?
Yes, it is. I guess so, since we have a new group now,
We have a new leader and new members,
I hope we can show you a lot of the new Angelem,
We are trying to do our best to present a new image of Angstrom to you all.
We, Beyoncé, have not changed in that way,
There is no change in the members or the organization,
This summer tour is an encore performance of the spring tour,
This summer tour is an encore performance of the spring tour.
The summer tour is an encore of the spring tour,
We had to make some changes, such as upgrading the version of the song. I think it was a concert that everyone could enjoy even more,
I think this concert will be more enjoyable for everyone,
I hope you will come and see the concert with such expectations.
I am looking forward to seeing you.
On a different note, this Halo! Ste. will be distributed on July 26th,
The day before, on the 25th, I, Hirayama, celebrated my 17th birthday.
Happy birthday!
Thank you very much.
Seventeen years old?
Yes, I turned 17.Yes, I turned 17.
I am 17 years old, everyone.
Yes, I am.
As I am 17 years old, I want to show you my cool side, but I also want to do my best to show you my cute side, which is typical of a 17 year old,
I would also like to do my best to show my 17-year-old side, which is cute and charming.
I enjoyed your performance at Yokohama Arena the day before,
Yuki's maturity?
You were 16 years old at that time, right?
I really like her cute 16-year-old expression,
I really like her cute 16-year-old expressions and her sudden moments,
I hope to see you in many different ways in your 17th year.
So, once again, happy birthday.
Thank you very much.
Now then, please take a look at this video.
Here you go!
I wonder if it's the summer
Whose fault is it?
A little unstable.
I'm the type of person whose hard work is doomed.
You're six centimeters off the ground.
Oh, oh, fashionable.
Tomorrow, I mean... You're so unique.
My ideal type. Yoo, that's weird.
Oh, Oh
Collage of emotions Reverb of love
Wave of passion, gulp of heat
Is it the summer, or a dream, or a little emotional instability?
I don't know whose fault it is... yours... I don't know who it is...
Sunshine, thunder, fireworks, bang, it's the season for flamboyance.
A woman's heart and the summer sky... whimsical and capricious... seven changes... a little emotionally unstable...
Which do you like better, spring or Akita?
A group shot in the late afternoon
You ask, so I'll answer seriouslyYou ask, so I'll answer seriously.
I'm sorry. I like summer.
I love summer... all the fun and games... until the sun goes down.
It's just so much fun, you know?
I'm just trying to be funny while I drink my acid.
I can feel the way you look at me.
Ah, ah, ah, I'll pop!
I'm making a face, I'm making a face
You're smiling even though you look terrible
Oh Oh Oh, you're a dreamer with delusions
Could it be Mylar Bar?
What are you looking at all your life, what the hell is going on
What the hell is going on?
I wonder if I'm dreaming A little unsteady, a little upbeat
Is this what love looks like? I don't think so.
What a waste of color. All of it.
I'm quaking, I'm quaking, I'm quaking, I'm quaking, I'm quaking, I'm quaking, I'm quaking
It's summer with you.
A woman's heart and the summer sky
Whimsical, whimsical, whimsical
A little bit of heartbreak, a little bit of ups and downs, a little bit of instability
Summer!
Jump!
I wonder if it's the summer, or if it's a dream, or if it's just a little unstable.
I don't know whose fault it is... yours... or mine.
I wonder if it's summer, or a dream, or something a little unstable
I wonder if it's love.
Is it summer?
You're saying that?
A little unstable.A little unstable.
Whose fault is it?
You, you, you.
I'm not sure who it is.
Summer is the season when fireworks are bursting
Summer's in the air from the girls
To the shadowy horizon
A little upbeat, a little unstable
Summer!
Senkyu!
Please subscribe to our channel!
With Yuki Hirayama of Angelem,
Beyonz Amemuro Koumi's Kurumi Takase is here with Halo! Stay!
From here, we'd like to talk a little bit about each other.
I'm going to ask you some questions, so don't think too much and answer them quickly.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Today's fashion point is
Don't give up on summery and cute with tulle material.
Yes.
Performing as Koumi Amemuro at Tokyo Idol Festival on August 4
How do you feel the difference from performing as Beyonce?
More emphasis on the world view of the songs
Ms. Takase as a guest performer at the renewal performance of Stage Vanguard by Ms. Yoshikazu Miyamoto
Is there anything in particular that you were conscious of in your performance?
Stir up the scene in a funny way
Oh!
Is there anything you are conscious of when deciding on a hairstyle for the tour?
To make it easy for fans to find me, I try not to cover my silhouette.
Mm-hm.
You do a lot of voice work.
Is there anything in particular you are conscious of to keep your voice in good condition during this season?
Talk to my throat.
Ooh.Oh!
Thank you very much.
How's the conversation going?
I said conversation.
I'm always aware of what's going on in my throat.
I mean, it's like you're always aware of what's going on with your throat.
It's like being aware of what's going on with your throat.
Not only at this time of the year, but all the time.
That's great. I will learn from you.
And when you appeared as a guest in the renewal performance, I was very impressed with the way you stirred things up.
I was very impressed with the way you stirred things up, and now I'm hearing about it.
What was it like?
This Stage Vanguard production starring Yoshikazu Miyamoto was the very first production I saw.
I went to see it when it first started.
I thought it was a performance I didn't like at all.
I see.
Perfect.
From the beginning to the end, Ms. Miyamoto and the cast were perfect.
The cast has created a wonderful worldview, and that's why I'm so happy to be a guest.
That's why I'm here as a guest.
I have to make the people who come and see the show laugh.
Or maybe it's because I'm making a change.
It's also because I really like ad-libbed parts when I see a play.
I want the cast on stage and the audience to be surprised at the moment when they are performing.
I enjoyed doing it in my own way.
It was a lot of fun!
It was amazing.
I learned a lot of things that I wasn't fully aware of.
I would like to use it as a reference.
Thank you very much.
Questions for Yuki Hirayama after the VTR
Hallo! Sta.
Is it because of summer or a dream?Maybe it's the summer, maybe it's a dream, maybe I'm just a little unstable.
Tea lady! New single!
Slightly Emotionally Unstable Summer on sale now!
Auntie Tea's new single! New single!
Auntie of Tea! Mahalo ba! Ikaenova!
Showa and 2025 are Wachamacha! Now on sale!
Shekena! The power to believe in oneself... Ordinary but forbidden!
Tea lady! New single!
Shekenare! Now on sale!
I can't choose just one, I can't choose just one, I can't choose just one, I can't choose just one, I can't choose just one, I can't choose just one, I can't choose just one, I can't choose just one, I can't choose just one
I wanted to love you, I couldn't love you
I couldn't love you I couldn't love you I couldn't love you I couldn't kiss you it's okay
You couldn't even take me away from you
Chuse Chuse PRIDE BRITE now on sale
Oh Let's play Lovely Music
Let's dance Disco till morning Let's
Chuse Chuse Funky Flushing now on sale
Hallo! Ste.
Next, I would like to ask Yuki Hirayama a question!
Yes please!
It was about 4 years ago when I joined the Halo Pro trainees.
What do you think has changed the most since then?
My ability to see things objectively.
Yuki Hirayama, the first junior member.
What kind of a senior do you want to be?
A senior member who is close to me.
The summer tour has started!
In what ways do you want to show the evolution of Yuki Hirayama?
Strongest as a constant
Cool!
Which Beyonce song would you like to sing?
Hamu katsu mehaku ku
S/mileage's "No need to work hard in this year" was released 13 years ago now.
Have you thought recently that you don't have to work so hard?Have you thought lately that you don't have to work so hard?
I'm not bound by stereotypes.
Oh!
That's kind of a cool answer to all of them.
Oh, no.
That's cool.
No, no, no, no, not at all.
Can I just ask you this?
What is it?
Which Beyonce song would you like to sing?
Hamu katsu meshiraku.
At Hello Project concerts, in the sleeves or something.
I've had a lot of opportunities to see Beyonce perform up close and personal.
That's when I decided that I wanted to do Hamakatsu.
My friend Shiori Nishida
I want to try it.
Also, there is a dance in the chorus where the line moves in formation.
I really wanted to do that with Anju.
And this one...
Taka-san sings in the middle and his hands are all over the stage. That's right. I really want to see it.
I would love to see it at Anju. I want to do it at Anju.
Now, there is one more thing. You have your first junior member, Yuki-chan. What kind of a senior do you want to be? A close senior?
Yes, a familiar senior. A familiar senior member. Yes, that's right. When I joined Anju, my three seniors and Mr. Takeuchi talked to me a lot,
I think that is the reason why my life at Anju is so comfortable, both at work and in private,
I want to be close to those two, so I really responded to them.
Oh, wow.
Yes.
And I think it's great to see that kind of atmosphere in Anju Room,
Yes, and I think it is wonderful to see that kind of atmosphere in Anju Room.
I hope we will be able to pay attention to your behavior as a senior member from now on.
Yes, I will do my best. I will do my best.
Halo! Stay tuned for more after this.
Thank you for watching.
This is Natsuyaki Masashi. Hello Kitchen has begun. This time, we have these members here.This is Masashi Natsuyaki. Here we are at Hello Kitchen. This time, we have a member here.
This is Minami Okamura from Beyonce. I'm Minami Okamura from Beyonce.
I'll do my best.
Please give my best.
Yes, I'm Minami Okamura. I look forward to working with you.
Please take care of it. So, what would you like to make?
Yes. Today's dish is... what?
Cheese Kulture.
Oh!
I don't know, it's hard to say.
What is it?
It's Indian, isn't it?
Yes. I would like to make cheese kulcher.
I'm going to make it by hand from the dough.
From the dough. I'm looking forward to it.
Yes, I'm looking forward to it. The ingredients are like this.
Okamura-chan, have you ever heard of cheese kulcha?
I like to watch videos of people cooking and making sweets, and I've seen it before. I've never had it yet, but I was curious about it because it looked so delicious.
Let's have fun making it. If you have any questions, please feel free to ask the teacher.
Let's get started right away.
Let's start by making the dough.
For bread, we usually use strong flour, and for tempeh, light flour.
For bread, we use light flour. For tempeh, we use light flour, but for breads that are more chunky, we use heavy-duty flour.
The most characteristic thing is that yogurt is added.
It doesn't work so well. We don't usually put it in bread.
Normally you don't put yogurt in bread, but only in naan.
Let's start with the raking powder.
4 grams. Put it all in.
I've made bread before.
I made it for Mother's Day with my father.
I made melon bread. It looked difficult.
But it didn't look good.
But your mom must have cried. I'm sure she's happy.
I added salt, sugar and baking soda.Salt, sugar, and baking soda are also included in this recipe.
If it's not distributed properly, it will expand in some places and not in others.
It's okay.
And I warmed the milk to about 40 degrees.
I heated the milk to about 40 degrees, and put the yogurt in it.
150 cc of milk, 30 grams of yogurt.
If you put the yogurt directly into the milk, it won't mix well.
So I put the yogurt directly into the milk, and then I mix it with the liquid.
Here's the yogurt that's gone.
I heated it up so it dissolves easily.
Half in the middle.
A little more. A little more.
A little more. Let's say that one more time, and mix it up a little bit with a spatula.
Yes.
That's good. Yes.
Then, let's add a little more for the teacher, shall we?
Yes. Please do.
Okamura-chan is a little bit like a girl who cooks.
Something like a girl who cooks.
A little bit. Yes, a little.
A little nervous. I'm always nervous.
I'm afraid my hands are going to shake.
No, no, no, no.
It's starting to come together in a whisper, and that's OK.
OK, OK.
Okay.
First of all, collect them here with your hands.
Gather it up.
With both hands...
What? I don't understand at all.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
Gather it up. Gather it up.Collect. Collect.
You don't have to know. Not at all.
It's fine. It's fine. It is coherent.
It's coming together.
Yes, it is.
Next, this way.
This one?
Yes, this one.
You've been doing this for a long time?
Yes, that's right.
Then, please keep working on it.
Okay.
There is no instruction, is there?
Just knead it like this.
Knead like this.
Yes, so that you don't make it into anything.
It's a little sticky, so knead it like this.
Here, just a little bit of kneading.
Yes, like this.
Isn't this a little rough now?
Yes, and here's where it's lumpy...
Yabiz point! Forming gluten.
What's it called? It's like a sticky type.
The sticky stuff comes out and bonds with the gluten.
They're not bonded now.
They're all in pieces.
They're all a little bumpy.
By connecting...
By connecting hand in hand...
When it's tight, it forms a membrane.
And air will enter the membrane and it will expand.
If the hands are not connected, the air will escape and it will not inflate.
This is how I imagine it.
You have to give it a lot of stimulation.You have to give them quite a bit of stimulation.
The gluten doesn't form.
Woah!
Put a little more force into it.
The sound is totally different.
It's like, "Shhhh.
It's like, "Let's do it.
With the usual stress.
Boom.
Oh, my God.
How's it looking? Is it shiny?
Yeah, it's looking good.
You're holding hands.
Like stretching.
Yes, sir.
Yes, yes.
Luxurious work.
It takes a lot of strength
It's like "nan", isn't it?
It's very resilient.
It's good, isn't it?
Looks good.
How much more is enough?
That's enough.
It's good enough?
Yes, it is.
Oh, it's beautiful.
I think it's good.
It's all there.
Okay.
Then cut this into four. Cut it into quarters.
It already looks delicious. It looks delicious.
The stickiness is due to the formation of gluten.This sticky feeling is gluten forming.
Oh, my gosh.
But the mussiness is actually a sign that carbonation is already taking place inside.
But the mottling is actually evidence that carbonation is already taking place inside.
So, if you put them together as much as possible, you can port them out.
If you put them together as much as possible
It's not going to run away.
I think it's a good idea.
Yes, sir.
Then it's done.
It's done.
Wrap it up.
In here.
It's warm.
Let's put it here for a minute.
It's about 35 degrees.
Yes, sir.
About 10 minutes.
That's right.
Let it rest.
Yes, sir.
That's all for this time.
We'll finish next time.
Let's do our best!
Please look forward to the next issue.
This way, please.
Here we go!
Oh, my gosh!
It looks like an ounce of something!
Bon appétit!
I'm so happy.I'm so glad I did it!
It's growing, it's growing, it's growing
It's growing, it's growing, it's growing.
Wow, absolutely delicious!
I'm so happy.
I feel like I'm being taught a technique, so I'm learning a lot.
Sounds like fun.
Yes, it is.
How about cooking, Mr. Nakajima?
I like cooking a lot.
That's nice.
I'm sure there's the kneading of flour when making something like that.
I really like cooking with flour and making sweets.
I recently baked three kinds of pound cakes.
I want to try snakes!
I baked 3 kinds of tea, cocoa and coffee.
I'd like to make a set to compare them.
I'd like that.
You've tried it, right?
It's good.
What about you, Segi-chan?
Well, I don't do much.
My mom cooks for me, so I spend my time eating it.
I'd like to try my best to cook for Valentine's Day and other occasions.
Hello! sta.
Yuki Hirayama of Angelem and
Beyonce, Ameino Mori, Minoru Kawao, Kurumi Takase, and I will be presenting the "Halo! STE
Project is celebrating its 25th anniversary this year. Project celebrates its 25th anniversary this year!
Project's 25th anniversary this year. Project's 25th anniversary this year, we'd like to introduce you to some of our favorite music videos with impressive costumes from the 25 years of Hello!
I'd like to start from the beginning.
I'd like to start with Berryz KOBO's "Koi no Jubaku" (Spellbound in Love).
This song is about a school uniform, which I think is very unusual.
I admire it so much.
I really like it.I like it very much.
If I had to pick one thing, it would be that there are so many scenes where he's catching a cold.
I was under the impression that this was the way music videos were supposed to be directed before I joined Halo! I had the impression before I joined Halo!
I wanted to catch a cold when I shoot music videos.
I was secretly thinking that I would like to catch a cold when I shoot music videos.
That's what impressed me about this music video.
Berryz KOBO
How will you protect me?
I don't have any grounds or anything
me
Stop being so geeky
And stop with the serious face
I know my friends like you.
Thank you for watching.
Friendship between women doesn't get any faster than this.
The curse of love.
Hello! Sta.
Next, I, Kurumi Takase, choose an impressive music video with an outfit.
I choose Morning Musume。 I choose Morning Musume。
This song also has members wearing uniforms and so on,
Some of the members wore suits that matched their characters, while others wore glasses,
Some of the members wore suits or glasses,
I really like the costumes that show the individuality of the members,
The direction of this music video is a bit theatrical.
The music video is a bit theatrical in its direction,
Actually, Beyonce and I did the same kind of music video for this song.
There is a boy with glasses,
I was very impressed that we were able to shoot a music video that was similar to a girl's story that I had always wanted to be a part of,
I was so impressed by the fact that we were able to shoot a music video similar to the one I had always wanted to do.
Maybe it's my talent for a moment.
I found a great cake shop, please take me there!
Wow Wow Wow Wow, there's a lot to be said for youth.
2, 3, 3, if it piles up, Kashimashi, Kashimashi, KashimashiTwo, three, three, when it piles up, Kashimashi, Kashimashi, Kashimashi
Takahashi, Airiko!
Airiko bang!
You're usually very conscious of it.
You're usually very conscious of it and say it doesn't match.
But when it's beats, it's right there.
Hometown dialect
Lady Rainflown.
Hey! Michishige!
To the corner supermarket in Supin
Got on the train in Supin
How about Brick in Supin?
I like it.
Go again.
Yes!
Ha!
Wow wow wow spirit
There's a lot going on here.
To the game.
Keep moving forward and business will prosper
The day we decided on the date and time of the party
You can't call 'em, they're all overflowing
I shouldn't have sent it to that girl.
I think he sent it.
Head room
It's blue.
I just can't decide on the bangs.
The more obvious it is, the more headroom it has.
Shortcake or something.
It's so easy to see.
Yes!
Wow Wow Wow Wow YouthWow Wow Wow Wow Youth
You know, there's a lot that goes into it.
Oh, when two or three of us get together, we win, we win, we win
Why do people fight?
When we should be working hand in hand
But it's black and white
There's a battle here
Speaking of which, mushrooms, bamboo shoots, bamboo shoots, bamboo shoots, bamboo shoots, bamboo shoots, bamboo shoots, bamboo shoots, bamboo shoots, bamboo shoots, bamboo shoots, bamboo shoots, bamboo shoots, bamboo shoots
I think it's the mushrooms. No, the bamboo shoots.
You're all right. I'm talking to you.
I don't know what's wrong with you. I feel sorry for you.
You're so stubborn. Just say it.
Mushrooms, bamboo shoots, bamboo shoots, bamboo shoots, bamboo shoots, bamboo shoots.
It's a lot for people who don't care.
I wonder if they laugh at the futility of the conflict.
But it's justice itself.
No one's creed is corrupted.
Though games beget more games
For my truth, there is only one answer
Though hate begets more hate
But to break this chain of events
Victory is impossible, impossible, impossible
Where there is no compromise
Selection, ICHIYOKA masters.
Two, six, mushrooms.
Naturally, Takase Meijin.
Three, eight, bamboo shoots.
It was a heated battle of take, take, take!
Lunch break here!
What's Meg's name?
Ichiyoka Meijin, of course it's mushrooms!
Takase Meijin, of course, played bamboo shoots.
apparently for the VTR
nene.
It's funny how we fight.
You're missing out on what's really important.
You need to take a look inside yourself.
It's not that I don't like you, it's just that I didn't want to admit it.
I can't shake my feelings for you, but I'll accept it.
Subtitle: Kiyohiroi
[Music]
Yes, there is no perfect peace.
I know it's sad
But while accepting each other
There must be a way to live together
Because we have love.
We have a heart that only thinks.
No one should hurt anyone
Come on, hand in hand
LaLaLaLa...
Each company is called somewhere sometimes dedicated
But the two sides will never fully understand
Gluttony. That's the way of man.
That's the way of life
With each other's strength
Our paths will widen
Wider, everlasting
The heart of bamboo, eternal.
[Applause]
Let's do our best tomorrow!
Beyons, Mino Amemorikawa, Kurumi Takase has sent you Halo! Ste. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11
It's time to say goodbye, so here's an announcement from us.
Hello Project 2023 Summer City Circuit is now underway!
And Beyonce will be performing at Yokosuka Art Theater on August 13th!
We are looking forward to bringing you an even more powerful summer tour, so we hope you will come and enjoy it.
And we, Angelem, will be performing at the Rock in Japan Festival 202 3 on August 13th.
We are very excited to be the first performer on the glass stage, and it will be our first festival as a new group, so we will do our best.We are very excited to be the top performer on the Glass Stage, and this will be our first festival as a newly organized group, so we will do our best.
Next, we, Beyons, will perform at Tokyo Idol Festival 2023 on August 4th and 5th.
On August 4, we will be performing as a group called "Subway," "Rain Forest," "Kawao," and "Seasonings," and on August 5, we will be performing as Beyons.
On August 5th, we will be performing as the Beyons, and I think there are many colors that only each unit can bring out.
I'm sure each unit will have its own unique color, so you can enjoy that, and as the Beyons, we'll make the summer hotter and hotter.
We will do our best to make it even more exciting and hotter, so please check us out!
The "Hello! Hello Project members will be appearing more and more on this channel. New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel!
This time we have Yuki Hirayama from Angulum and Kurumi Takase from Beyons, Ame no Mori, Kawao Mino and Mino.
Good bye.